<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Metro Developer</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Metro Developer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>d&#43;air: data artist in residence</title>
      <link>/posts/digital-art-residency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/digital-art-residency/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Each piece can be placed on a continuum, with art on one end and data visualization on the other, and ranging between adjectives: ambiguous/concrete, personal/public, intuitive/objective, informational/emotional. No matter where the maps fall, their creators are communicating underlying verities—whether evidence-based truths or more pliant, relative “truths”—about life in an endlessly fascinating and dynamic metropolis.
http://lab.culturalanalytics.info/2017/09/on-broadway-on-view-in-exhibition-you.html
Data Artist-in-Residence Vision Metro posits that artists are well-positioned to synthesize diverse facts, goals, data and references, reveal new frames, connections and meaning and speak across “languages” as it applies to problem-solving, knowledge creation, and enhancing the user experience for Metro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/posts/privacy-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/privacy-statement/</guid>
      <description>The Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transportation Authority (Metro) respects your privacy. The following describes our Privacy Policy in relation to the information you submit via Metro’s WordPress websites such as:  The Source: Transportation News &amp;amp; Views website address is: http://thesource.metro.net/ El Pasajero: Tu ruta directa a novedades de transporte website address is: http://elpasajero.metro.net/ Metro Annual Report website address is: http://annualreport.metro.net/ Measure M: Metro’s Plan to Transform Transportation website address is: http://theplan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>/posts/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo!</title>
      <link>/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-1-install-hugo&#34;&gt;Step 1. Install Hugo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/spf13/hugo/releases&#34;&gt;hugo releases&lt;/a&gt; and download the
appropriate version for your os and architecture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More complete instructions are available at &lt;a href=&#34;/overview/installing/&#34;&gt;installing hugo&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;move-static-content-to-static&#34;&gt;Move static content to &lt;code&gt;static&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with &lt;code&gt;_&lt;/code&gt; will be copied as-is to the &lt;code&gt;_site&lt;/code&gt; output. Hugo keeps all static content under &lt;code&gt;static&lt;/code&gt;. You should therefore move it all there.
With Jekyll, something that looked like&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/
    ▾ images/
        logo.png
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>